杰森:麦琪,如果我们现在不出发的话,
Jason: Maggie, if we don't leave now we are going to miss the start of
我们要错过电影的开头.
that movie.
麦琪:没关系.我只是去看梅尔 吉布森.
Maggie: I don't care.I'm just going to see Mel Gibson.
杰森:记住,迈克,克莉丝的睡觉时间是……
Jason: Remember Mike, Chrissy's bedtime is...
迈克:嘿!你们说还有一个小时呀.
Mike: Hey!you told me it was in an hour.
麦琪:现在
Maggie: Right now.
克莉丝:你们走吧.我们解决.
Chrissy: You guys go.We'll work it out.
杰森:再见.哎,
Jason: see you.Hey, when you get Chrissy to bed,
当你把克莉丝弄上床睡觉之后,注意打扫厨房.
look into cleaning up that kitchen.
还有前面走廊的几个灯泡坏了,换一下.
And we ave a few light bulbs out on the front porch that could use changing.
还有记得顶楼的地板要磨光,如果你……
And remember that floor sander up in the attic, if you...
迈克:喔,喔.爸爸,行了.我只是临时照顾孩子.
Mike: Wow, wow.Dad, come on.I'm just babysitting here.
杰森:迈克,接下来四个小时,你可以得到高报酬.
Jason: mike, you are being very well paid for the next four hours.
迈克:高报酬!是呀,以西维尔信誉.
Mike: Well paid!Yeah, in Seaver credits.
杰森:如果你不做这些家务事,你将什么都得不到.
Jason: Well if you don't do those chores, you are not going to get anything.
克莉丝:灯泡换好了.
Chrissy: The light bulbs are changed.
迈克:很好!然后你最好开始打扫厨房.
Mike: Alright!Well then you just better get started on the kitchen.
克莉丝:我更喜欢开萝尔照看孩子.
Chrissy: I like it better when Carol baby-sits.
迈克:嗨,别唠叨了,克莉丝.我们不应该嫉妒她一年一度的约会.
Mike: Hey now.Come on Chrissy.We can't begrudge her her yearly date.
本:唷.嗨,你在照顾孩子吗?
Ben: Yo.Hey, are you babysitting?
迈克:是呀.
Mike: Yeah.
本:我在和克莉丝说话.
Ben: I was talking to Chrissy.
克莉丝:我喜欢这样.
Chrissy: I like that.
迈克:啊,你在嘲笑我?
Mike: Ah, you're laughing hu?
本:当然.
Ben: Yeah.
迈克:听好,妈妈和爸爸让我给你们一些严格的规定.
Mike: Well, mum and dad left me some strict orders for you.
他们要你们进去把厨房弄干净.然后,
They want you to get in there and clean up the kitchen.
你知道要把顶楼的地板磨光?他们还要求你们去,
And then, you know that floor sander in the attic?
去什么,去什么……
They want you to, to uh, to uh..
本:去干什么?
Ben: To what?
迈克:嗨,如果我是你,
Mike: Hey, if I were you pal, I'd stop asking questions and just get to it.
伙计,我就少问多做.很好!
Alright!I got the big kid doing the chores and I got the little kid in
我把大的弄去干家务活,我把小的弄上床.
bed.
克莉丝:我只想让你知道.我高你一等.
Chrissy: I just wanted you to know, I'm a step ahead of you.
迈克:嘿,嘿,进来,埃迪.
Mike: hey hey, com on in Eddie.
埃迪:哟!
Eddie: Yo!
埃迪:唉,米歇尔,今晚你打算干什么?
Eddie: So, Michael, what you got going this evening?
迈克:埃迪,我碰巧要照看孩子.
Mike: Well Eddie, I just happen to be babysitting.
埃迪:啊.
Eddie: Ah.Then you wouldn't be interested in the promised land of available
那么你就不会对那个有美女的乐土感兴趣了.
babes?
迈克:喔,喔,喔.埃迪.什么有美女的乐土?
Mike: Wow, wow, wow.Eddie.What do you mean the promised land of available babes?
埃迪:哦,米歇尔,
Eddie: Oh Michael, I have been to the mountain top and I have seen the
我曾经到达山顶,我看到了另一侧.
other side.It is a place filled with beautiful women, passionate women,
那是一处充满美女的地方,充满激情,十分饥渴的女人.
hungry women.Michael, it's a place where they treat men like red meat
米歇尔,那是一处女人对男人就向对待扔进他们笼子里面的鲜肉一样.
thrown into their cages.
迈克:等会,这个地方在新泽西州,是不是?
Mike: Wait a minute, this isn't that place in New Jersey is it?
埃迪:走吧,迈克.我们出发吧.
Eddie: Come on Mike.Let's go.
迈克:不,我不能.我已经告诉你,埃迪,我在照看孩子.
Mike: No, I can't.I told you Eddie, I'm babysitting.
埃迪:本已经十四岁了.他不需要有人照看.
Eddie: Ben's fourteen.He doesn't need a sitter.
迈克:不,不,不.克莉丝也在这.
Mike: No, no, no.Chrissy's here.
埃迪:那么本就没问题了.
Eddie: Another reason Ben will be fine.
迈克:如果我不能找到其他人来照看小孩,我就不能和你出去.
Mike: I cannot go out with you until I find some other sucker to baby-sit.
开萝尔:我不在乎距离我上次约会有多长时间.
Carol: I don't care how long it's been since my last date.
我不会去和一个连你好都说不好的男孩子出去约会.
I refuse to go out with a guy who burps hello.
埃迪:你好.
Eddie: Hello.
迈克:哦,埃迪,
Mike: Oh Eddie come on.Don't do that.Can't you see the girl is hurting here?
过来.别这样做.
I mean come on.
你没看见那个女孩正伤心着吗?我说的是,
Why can't she find a decent guy who would appreciate her for the catch
为什么她找不到一个迷上她,欣赏她的好男孩?
that she is?
开萝尔:你拿我寻开心?
Carol: Is that a fish joke?
迈克:不,我是说,你是个好人,家庭观念很强.
Mike: No, I'm just saying that you are a decent person with great family values.
开萝尔:那是.
Carol: That's true.
迈克:是的,还有你很忠实.你是那种能够放弃一切事情来照看自己小妹妹的女孩.
Mike: Yeah and you are loyal to.You are the kind of girl who would
drop everything just to baby-sit your baby sister
开萝尔:你相信我是这样的.
Carol: You bet I would.
迈克:再见.
Mike: See you.
本:爸爸说我从来没在这里干过事情.
Ben: And dad says I never do anything around here.
迈克:埃迪.我们到底在哪?
Mike: Eddie.Where the heck are we?
埃迪:天堂.
Eddie: heaven.
马克:埃迪,那些是什么人?
Mike: Eddie, who are these people?
埃迪:单身父母.
Eddie: Parents without mates.
迈克:我要走了.
Mike: I'm leaving.
埃迪:你走吧,迈克.
Eddie: Alright mike fine.More for me.
我很好.
See I don't know about you,
但是我不知道你感觉怎么样,但是我很高兴找到一处能够放松和恢复的好地方.
but I'm just happy to find a place where I can relax and be myself.
女士:爱德华,哦,你好!欧洲怎么样?
Lady: Edward, oh hi!How was Europe?
埃迪:好极了.
Eddie: Excellent.
女士:哦,很好.
Lady: Oh great.
埃迪:这是墙的一片.
Eddie: Here's a piece of the wall.
女士:哦,谢谢.
Lady: Oh thank you.
埃迪:我是从停车场拣来的.她却如此高兴.
Eddie: I got it from the parking lot.She's so happy.
迈克:埃迪,我所要说的是这不是我的想法……
Mike: Eddie, look all I'm saying is that this is just not my idea...
女孩:请问.这是36C吗?
Girl: Excuse me.Is this thirty six C?
埃迪:是36C.
Eddie: thirty six C.
迈克:是的,这是的.
Mike: yeah, yeah it is.
领导:大家好,女士们,先生们.现在可以开始了吗?
Leader: Alright Ladies and gentlemen.Shall we begin?
埃迪:再见,迈克.
Eddie: See you Mike.
迈克:我想我可以待一两分钟.
Mike: I think I may stay for a minute or two.
领导:我发现今晚来了一些新人.
Leader: I see we have some newcomers this evening.
你们能告诉大家你们的名字和你们怎么成为单身父母的?
Do you want to tell us your name and how you became a single parent?
迈克和女孩:哦,我……
Mike and Girl: Oh see I...
迈克:我想是你……
Mike: I thought you...
女孩:我不知道……
Girl: I didn't know...
迈克:不,请吧,女士优先.
Mike: No please, ladies first.
女孩:对我来说这些比较陌生.如果大家没什么意见的话,
Girl: This is all a little new to name.
我想先听会儿再说.
So if it's ok for everyone, I'd just like to listen for a while.
领导:没意见.好的.
Leader: That is more than ok.Yes.
迈克:她还没自报家门.
Mike: She didn't give her name.
女孩:我叫蕾切尔.
Girl; I'm Rachel.
每个人:你好,蕾切尔.
Everyone: Hi Rachel.
迈克:很好,我叫迈克.
Mike: Great, I'm Mike.
每个人:你好,迈克.
Everyone: Hi Mike.
女士2:他说他爱孩子,但是当问题变的严重时,
Lady 2: He said he loved kids, but when things started getting serious,
他就说了句"娜塔莉,我走了".
he said "Natalie, I'm gone".
埃迪:(哭)别说了,你这让我心碎.
Eddie: (Crying) Please, you're tearing me up.
迈克:我不认识他.我刚刚在大厅碰上他的.
Mike: I don't know.I just met him in the hall.
领导:我想今天就到此为止,在此我感谢大家今晚能来参加.
Leader: I see we are just about out of time,
晚安.
and I want to thank you all for coming this evening.Goodnight.
蕾切尔:谢谢.
Rachel: Thanks.
迈克:不用客气了.
Mike: You're welcome.
蕾切尔:今晚来这我真的很开心.
Rachel: I'm really glad I came tonight.
迈克:哦,我也是.我也是,我叫迈克.
Mike: Oh me too.Me too.I'm Mike.
蕾切尔:你告诉我很多次了.
Rachel: You've said that several times.
迈克:我只是想让你知道我的名字没变.啊,这样,
Mike: I just want to let you know it hasn't changed.
噢,你想出去吗?吃点什么?
Ah, so, uh, uh, you feel like going out?Maybe getting something to eat?
蕾切尔:我?
Rachel: Me?
迈克:是呀,现在才九点半.
Mike: Yeah, I mean it's only nine thirty.
蕾切尔:我还要照看孩子.
Rachel: What about my babysitter?
迈克:哦,好吧,但我很想和你出去.
Mike: Oh, ok, but I'd rather go out with you.
蕾切尔:我得凉快凉快.
Rachel: I have to cool off.
迈克:哦,想法一致.这就出去凉快.
Mike: Oh what a coincidence.So cool out here.
蕾切尔:小伙子,这个巷子使我回忆起从前.
Rachel: Boy, does this alley bring back memories for me.
哦,
Oh, back in Veterinary High,
回到了维特瑞纳里高中,我和小伙伴们经常潜入阿奥家.
this is how me and my friends used to sneak into Al's.
迈克:喔,喔,等一下.你上维特瑞纳里高中?我上的是杜威高中.
Mike: Wow, wo, wait a minute.You went to Veterinary?I went to Dewey.
蕾切尔:哦.是竞争对手.
Rachel: Oh.Rivals.
迈克:我知道.我知道.
Mike: I know.I know.
蕾切尔:哦,这听起来有点无话可说,
Rachel: Oh, this is going to sound dumb,
但是我今晚就像一个无忧无虑的大学生.
but I feel like a carefree college kid tonight.
迈克:是呀,是呀.我也能想起那一切.
Mike: Yeah, yeah.I can be reminded of that too.
蕾切尔:是的,上次我跳舞还是朱迪思的三岁生日.
Rachel: Yeah, the last time I went dancing was Judith's third birthday.
那是做个样子而已.
And it was the Hockey Cokey.
迈克:哦.谁是朱迪思?
Mike: Oh yeah.Who's Judith?
蕾切尔:哦,是我女儿.
Rachel: Oh my daughter.
迈克:你有个女儿?哦,
Mike: You have a daughter?Oh yeah right.
是,对.我还以为你有个儿子.
I thought you d\said you had a son.
蕾切尔:不,你有个儿子.
Rachel: No, you have a son.
迈克:那是.我有个儿子.
Mike: That's right.I do.
蕾切尔:刚才一会,我都忘了我们都有孩子了.
Rachel: For a minute there I forgot we both had kids.
迈克:我得谢谢你提醒我.
Mike: And I want to thank you for reminding me.
蕾切尔:你'儿子叫什么?
Rachel: What's your son's name?
迈克:啊,克莉丝.克莉丝 E 西维尔.
Mike: Ah it's Chrissy.Chris E Seaver.
蕾切尔:E代表什么?
Rachel: What does the E stand for?
迈克:爱尔维斯.哦,我前妻是个狂热者.
Mike: Elvis.Uh, yeah see my ex wife was a really big fan.
事实上,她离开我去找他了.开个玩笑.
In fact she left me to go find him.Just kidding.
蕾切尔:我也想拿我的前夫说笑.迈克,
Rachel: I wish I could laugh about my ex that way.
我今晚很开心.
Mike, I had a lovely time.
迈克:你怎么用过去时?继续,才十二点半.
Mike: What do you mean had?Come on, it's only twelve thirty.
蕾切尔:十二点半了!
Rachel: Twelve thirty!
迈克:是呀.怎么了?
Mike: Yeah.What's wrong?
蕾切尔:我告诉我保姆我十一点之前就回家.
Rachel: I told my sitter I'd be home by eleven.
迈克:就偷偷回去.蕾切尔.我什么时候还能再见到你?
Mike: Just sneak in.Ah Rachel.When can I see you again?
蕾切尔:恩,你想明天去野餐吗?
Rachel: Um, are you going to the picnic tomorrow?
迈克:呵,我都准备野餐几个星期了.什么野餐呀?
Mike: Ah, I've been planning on it for weeks.What picnic?
蕾切尔:单身父母野餐呀.
Rachel: The parents without mates picnic.
迈克:很好.
Mike: Oh right.
蕾切尔:你有机会见到我的朱迪思,
Rachel: You'll have a chance to meet my Judith and I can't wait to meet
我也迫不及待想见见你的克莉丝.
your Chris.
迈克:我也等不及了.
Mike: Neither can I.
杰森:你不觉得本磨了四分之一的油毡地板很奇怪吗?
Jason: And you didn't think Ben sanding away a quarter of an inch of linoleum
floor was a little odd?
麦琪:开萝尔,怎么回事?
Maggie: Carol, how could you let this happen?
开萝尔:等一下.你让谁负责的?
Carol: Wait a minute.Who did you put in charge?
杰森:迈克.
Jason: Mike.
开萝尔:谁磨地板了?
Carol: And who sanded the floor?
麦琪:本.
Maggie: Ben.
开萝尔:这怎么成了我的错?
Carol: So how did this become my fault?
杰森:开萝尔,你是我们最可信赖的孩子.
Jason: Carol, you are the most dependable child we have.We rely on you.
我们相信你.
You rarely let us down.
你不会让我们失望.像这种事情发生让我们很失望.
That's why it's so disappointing when something like this happens.
迈克:再见.克莉丝和我准备去公园.
Mike: See you guys.Chrissy and I are going to go to the park.
开萝尔:不错 .他出去享乐,
Carol: Oh great.He gets to go out and have fun and I get to sit
我坐在这里,却由于你们两个挨批,可以我什么都没做错.
here and be yelled at by you two and I didn't even do anything.
迈克:那是,问题就出在这,小姐.
Mike: Well that just may be the problem young lady.
克莉丝:怎么样,迈克?
Chrissy: How's that Mike?
迈克:不,不,不,不.这里,抓好方向盘,很好,现在谁是你爸爸?
Mike: No, no, no, no.Here, take the wheel.Alright, now who's your daddy?
克莉丝:你是爸爸.
Chrissy: You are dad.
迈克:说的对,很好.我知道了.好,很好.你是男孩还是女孩?
Mike: There you do, alright, I got it.Alright, very good.Are you a boy
or a girl
克莉丝:今天我是男孩.
Chrissy: Today I'm a boy.
迈克:十分好.现在我需要你把今天这部分去掉.
Mike: Very very good.Now I want you to forget about the today part.
克莉丝:我是男孩.我是男孩.我是男孩.
Chrissy: I'm a boy.I'm a boy.I'm a boy.
迈克:我希望我没有犯下严重错误.好,
Mike: I hope I'm not doing serious damage here.
还有最后一件事情.你中间的名字叫爱尔维斯.
Ok, there's only one more thing.Your middle name is Elvis.
克莉丝:你是说那个国王?
Chrissy: You mean the King?
迈克:好了,好了,好了.不要傻笑了.
Mike: Com eon, come on, come on.Stop giggling.Let's go Chris.
我们出发,克莉丝.这边走,这边走.
Here we go, here we go.
克莉丝:我想我的指甲坏了.
Chrissy: I think I broke a nail.
迈克:男孩子是不在乎坏指甲的.
Mike: Boys don't care about broken nails.
克莉丝:我也不在乎.
Chrissy: I don't either.
蕾切尔:你知道,如果我再婚有另外孩子的话,
Rachel: you know, if I ever got married again and had another child,
我想我会要个男孩.
I think I'd like a boy.
克莉丝:我是男孩.
Chrissy: I'm a boy.
蕾切尔:是的,小甜心,我知道.
Rachel: Yes sweetheart, I know that.
克莉丝:那是事实.
Chrissy: It's the truth.
孩子:迈克,我们玩了.
Kid: mike let's play.
迈克:好.
Mike: Ok.
克莉丝:是的.
Chrissy: Yeah.
迈克:我经常玩些小游戏.玩了,
Mike: I'm always up for a little play.Let's go, let's go.
玩了.你瞧,
Alright look, yesterday you felt like a college kid,
昨天你像一个大学生,
today you are going to feel like a four year old, and by third date,
今天你像四岁的孩子,第三天你就要裹尿布了.
you are going to be in diapers.
蕾切尔:我等不及了.
Rachel: I can't wait.
迈克:准备好了吗,孩子们?
Mike: Are you ready guys?
克莉丝:好了.
Chrissy: Ready.
迈克:好.我们来.一,二,三.
Mike: Ok.Here we go.One, two, three.
蕾切尔:恩,谈到第三次约会,我想如果可能……
Rachel: Um, speaking of a third date, I was wondering if maybe.....
迈克:哦,不.瞧,我会解释一切的.
Mike: Oh no.Ah look, I can explain everything.
本:爸爸,爸爸,爸爸.
Ben: Daddy, daddy, daddy.
女人:是你儿子?
Lady: That's your son?
埃迪:是的,他长的跟他妈一样大.
Eddie: Yeah, he's big like his mother.
蕾切尔:迈克,你说什么呢?
Rachel: Mike, you were saying?
迈克:没什么.没什么.你说什么呢?
Mike: Nothing.Nothing.You were saying?
蕾切尔:哦,我想说的是,
Rachel: Oh I was saying, speaking of a third date, um,
说到第三次约会,我想你不会很忙,你找个人照看小孩.
I was just wondering if you weren't busy tonight and you could get a sitter,
迈克:那不成问题.
Mike: That wouldn't be a problem.
蕾切尔:今晚来我家共进晚餐怎么样?
Rachel: So how about coming to my house for dinner tonight?
迈克:你做饭?
Mike: So you cook too?
蕾切尔:不.
Rachel: No.
迈克:我乐意去.
Mike: I would love to.
蕾切尔:很好.
Rachel: Yeah.
迈克:好的,我很乐意去.
Mike: Yeah, I would love to.
蕾切尔:也许告诉你这些是我犯的一个大错误,
Rachel: I'm probably making a big mistake telling you this,
但是我和你在一起感觉很安全.
but I feel safe with you.
迈克:是的吗?
Mike: You do?
蕾切尔:啊哈.我很久没有碰到我可以信任的人了.
Rachel: Uh hu.I haven't met anybody in a long time that I can trust.
本:真是个好爸爸.给我20美金去买冰淇淋.
Ben: What a great daddy.I gave me twenty dollars for the ice cream truck.
蕾切尔:给我那找的零钱,小伙子.
Rachel: I want my change young man.Or you won't sit for a week.
否则你别想清静.你明白了吗?
You got that pus bag?
迈克:不,我是认真的.她说她信任我.
Mike: No I'm serious.She says she trusts me.
埃迪:米歇尔,信任是女人可以给你的第二重要的方面,
Eddie: Michael, trust is the second most important thing a woman can give
因为没有信任的话,你就得不到第一个.
you, because without it you can't get the first
迈克:埃迪,告诉你.她之前受到过伤害.
Mike: Eddie, come on man.She's been hurt before.
埃迪:不是你的过错.
Eddie: Not your fault.
迈克:埃迪,她有个小女儿.
Mike: Eddie, she's got a little girl.
埃迪:这样,迈克.我明白你想什么.你感觉昨晚去那个单身父母晚会是个错误.你是对的.
Eddie: Alright Mike.I see what you are getting at.You feel it was a
mistake for you to go to Parents Without Mates last night.And you are right
迈克:是呀.
Mike: Ok.
埃迪:你应该去傻瓜父母俱乐部.
Eddie: You should have gone to parents without brains.
迈克:我赞成.
Mike: Yeah.
本:埃迪,我在楼下看到你的车了.
Ben: Eddie, I saw your car downstairs.
这是你买冰淇淋的钱的找零.
Here is your change form the ice cream money.
埃迪:三十七美分!在花了二十美金去买冰淇淋.
Eddie: Thirty seven cents!You wasted my twenty dollars on ice cream?
本:不.还买了一张新CD.
Ben: No.On a new CD.
埃迪:哦,不,不,不.我不要那东西.我可不是造钱的.
Eddie: Oh no no, no.Don't give me that.I'm not made of money.
本:好吧,爸爸,
Ben: Well dad, you should have thought of that before you brought me into
当你把我带到这个世界之前你应该想到这点.
this world.
迈克:嘿,打住,打住.别烦了.别烦了.现在给我走.
Mike: Hey, stop, stop.Cut it out.Cut it out.Now get out of here.
埃迪:是的,混蛋.
Eddie: Yeah fungus.
迈克:我也对你说的.
Mike: I'm talking to you too.
埃迪:哦,嗨,
Eddie: Oh, hey, fine.
好的.我给你带来了开心的消息,你却撵我滚蛋.
I've got some news that could cheer you up, but you're making me leave.
迈克:不,好,好了,什么消息?
Mike: No, alright, alright, what is it.
埃迪:好.你知道我的女朋友娜塔莉.
Eddie: Ok.You know my girlfriend Natalie?
迈克:知道.
Mike: Yeah.
埃迪:我刚刚发现她有一个跟我差不多大的女儿.
Eddie: Well I just found out that she's got a daughter my own age.
我想我们可以共同分享.
I think we are talking letters to Penthouse here.
迈克:滚出去.滚出去.
Mike: get out.Get out.
杰森:足够粘了.
Jason: It's tacky enough.
麦琪:别废话,杰森.
Maggie: No comment.Jason,
如果请人专业安装,岂不是更容易?
wouldn't it be easier if we had this professionally installed?
杰森:麦琪,那些人要三四百块呢.
Jason: Maggie, those guys get three, four hundred dollars.
麦琪:本,走开.
Maggie: Ben move.
本:不行.
Ben: I can't.
杰森:快点.我要在那里铺地毯.
Jason: Come on.I'm trying to lay linoleum in here.
本:那么你们为什么还要我磨地板呢?
Ben: Then what did you guys have Eddie: sand the floor for?
迈克:那是什么?
Mike: What's that?
本:哦,我的新CD.
Ben: Oh, my new cd.
麦琪:你哪来钱买的?
Maggie: Where did you get the money to buy this?
本:啊,钱.
Ben: Uh, money.
杰森:你应该没有钱的,本.
Jason: You don't have any money Ben.
本:我说我买的吗?我偷来的.
Ben: Did I say I bought it?I meant I stole it.
杰森:迈克!迈克!
Jason: Mike!Mike!
迈克:在这.
Mike: Yeah.
杰森:那个泥球在哪?埃迪?埃迪?
Jason: Where's that slime ball Eddie?Eddie?
迈克:他刚走.什么事?出什么事了?
Mike: Ah he just left.Why?Is something the matter?
杰森:本已经告诉我埃迪干了什么,很多.
Jason: After what Ben told me Eddie did, a lot.
迈克:埃迪干了些什么?
Mike: Eddie did something?
杰森:哦,是这样.他付钱给本,让本假装是他儿子,
Jason: Oh yeah.He actually paid Ben to pretend to be his son so Eddie
这样埃迪就可以接近那个容易上钩,毫无戒备的女人.你能想像出来吗?
could get closer to this vulnerable, unsuspecting woman.Can you imagine that?
迈克:我能.本还说了什么?
Mike: I can.Did Ben say anything else?
杰森:这些还不够吗?
Jason: Isn't that enough?
迈克:对我来说已经足够了.
Mike: It is for me.
杰森:周围就有这样的榜样,怎么能让本学会尊重妇女?
Jason: How's Ben supposed to learn to respect women when there is an example
我很高兴他还尊敬你,
like that around?I'm just glad that he still looks up to you Mike.
迈克.
I mean you have really done some hair brain things in you life,
我是说尽管你干过一些捣蛋的事情,但是你从来没有干出像这种伤天害理的下流事.
but you've never done anything as hurtful and scummy as that.
迈克:你不觉得你说的过重了吗,爸爸?
Mike: Don't you think you are being a little strong dad?
杰森:那你怎么看待呢,迈克?
Jason: How else would you describe it Mike?
在某人最脆弱的时候,从他身上获利?
When somebody takes advantage of somebody at there weakest moment like that?
迈克:我从来没有想过这些.
Mike: I never really thought of it like that.
我确信埃迪也没有真正思考过这些.
And I'm sure Eddie never really thought it through either.
杰森:你真不错,迈克.
Jason: That's nice of you mike.Sticking up for your friend like that.
你还为你这样的朋友辩护.我只是庆幸我儿子没有做出这样的事情.
I'm just glad that I don't have a son who would do something like that.
蕾切尔:迈克,你来的早呀.
Rachel: Mike, you're early.
迈克:你好,蕾切尔.
Mike: Hi.Rachel, there's some things that I've been thinking about and
有些事情我一直在思考,
there's some thing I really need to talk to you about and I don't think
有些事情我得告诉你,我想不应该再等了.
it should wait.
蕾切尔的妈妈:蕾切,我找不到朱迪斯的企鹅了.这应该就是你说的他了.
Rachel's mother: Rach, I can't find Jude's penguin.This has to be him.
蕾切尔:是的,妈妈,这是迈克 西维尔.迈克,这是我母亲,贝蒂.
Rachel: Yep.Mum, this is Mike Seaver.Mike this is my mother Betty.
蕾切尔的妈妈:见到你很高兴.
Rachel's mother: My pleasure.
蕾切尔:等一下.我拿朱迪斯的企鹅.
Rachel: excuse me.I'll just get Judith's penguin.
妈妈:对我而言,你看起来不笨.
Mother: You don't look so goofy to me.
迈克:哦,她肯定告诉你了.
Mike: Oh, well she told you about that.
蕾切尔:你记住迈克了.
Rachel: You remember Mike.
朱迪斯:记住!我们整天谈论他.
Judith: Remember!We were talking about him all day.
妈妈:我们得走了.我们去玩了.说晚安.
Mother: We should go.We are going to have such fun.Say goodnight.
蕾切尔:再见,妈妈.
Rachel: Bye mum.
妈妈:再见.
Mother: Bye.
朱迪斯:再见,妈妈.再见,迈克.
Judith: Bye mummy.Bye Mike.
妈妈:我们得走了.
Mother: We're off.
蕾切尔:迈克,你说什么不能再等了?
Rachel: So Mike, what was it that couldn't wait?
迈克:啊,也许可以等.
Mike: Ah, maybe it can wait.
蕾切尔:好吧,我去拿些开胃食品.
Rachel: Ok, I'll go get my appetizers.
迈克:不,我不能等了.
Mike: No, it can't wait.
蕾切尔:好的.
Rachel: Ok.
迈克:拿点开胃食品.
Mike: Get your appetizers.
蕾切尔:好.
Rachel: Ok.
迈克:不.
Mike: No.
蕾切尔:我可以,给你拿点喝的吗?
Rachel: can I uh, get you something to drink?
迈克:听着,蕾切尔,我不是我说的那样.我还没有结婚.
Mike: Look Rachel, I'm not who I said I was.I've never been married.
蕾切尔:还没有结过婚!
Rachel: Never been married!
迈克:还没有.
Mike: No.
蕾切尔:没什么.
Rachel: It's ok.
迈克:真的?
Mike: It is.
蕾切尔:你什么都不要解释.问题是我看见你和你儿子之间的爱.
Rachel: You don_t have to explain anything.
你要喝点什么?
All that matters is the love I see between you and your son.
酒,饮料还是果汁?
Can I get you something to drink?Wine, soft drink, puffball?
迈克:不,我儿子是女孩子.
Mike: Look, my son is a girl.
蕾切尔:什么?
Rachel: Pardon.
迈克:是克莉丝.克莉丝是我的小妹妹,
Mike: Yes Chris.Chris it_s my little sister Chrissy.
克莉丝.还有那个晚会上我说我不认识的混蛋就是埃迪.
And Eddie that sleazy guy at the meeting who I said I didn't know...
蕾切尔:那混蛋在中央情报局工作?
Rachel: The guy who works for the CIA?
迈克:是的,就是那个.
Mike: Yeah, that's the one.
瞧,他认为我们两个参加单身父母聚会是个好主意,
Look, he thought it would be a good idea if the two of us went down
认识一些姑娘.所以我就去参加了.
to the Parents Without Mates meeting, to meet some girls.So I went.
我不是个父亲.我什么都不是.
I'm not a father.I guess I'm not much of anything.Rachel, come on.
蕾切尔,你想说点什么?
Say something.
蕾切尔:你对我撒谎了.
Rachel: You lied to me.
迈克:听着,我……
Mike: Look, I...
蕾切尔:不.我认为你们不同.
Rachel: No.I thought you were different.
迈克:哎.别这样,蕾切尔.我知道你一定经历了很多,我不是想故意伤害你.说真的.
Mike: Look.Come on Rachel.I know you must have been through a lot and
I didn't meet to hurt you.Honest
蕾切尔:是呀,没人说自己会伤害别人,
Rachel: Yeah well nobody means to hurt anybody, but it still happens.
但是实际上已经伤害了.然道没有吗?
Doesn't it?
迈克:你看,今天晚上对我来说最简单的做法就是别在这里出现.
Mike: Look, the easiest thing in the world for me to have done tonight
你知道,我像个彻头彻尾的傻瓜站在这里的唯一原因是,
would have been to not show up here.
是你对于我来说很重要.你对我来说十分重要.
You know, but the only reason I am standing here acting like a complete
我意思是说,我真的在乎你,
fool is, is because you mean something to me.You mean a lot to me.
蕾切尔,我是说,
I mean I really do care about you Rachel and, I mean,
能让我们重新开始吗?你说呢?
can we just start over?Please.What do you say?
我是迈克 西维尔,我不是一个父亲.
My name's Mike Seaver and I'm not a father.
迈克:多谢,爸爸.没事了.
Mike: Thanks a lot dad.For nothing.
杰森:怎么回事,迈克?过来.坐下.
Jason: What's wrong Mike?Come here.Sit.
迈克:你想知道怎么回事?好吧,
Mike: You want to know what's wrong?Ok, I'll tell you what's wrong.
我告诉你怎么回事.埃迪对我生气了.
Eddie's mad at me.
杰森:他?
Jason: He is?
迈克:是的,因为我告诉他你对他有多生气.
Mike: Yes, because I told him how angry you were.
杰森:然后呢?
Jason: And?
迈克:然后,他决定单独去那姑娘家,
Mike: And, well he decided to go over to this girl_s house in person,
告诉那姑娘他说谎了,他真的没有小孩,
and tell her that he was lying to her and that he really didn't have children
请求原谅.这对他来说太难了,
and ask for her forgiveness.
爸爸,因为他准备走出那门,
It was really hard for him dad, because he was about to walk out the door,
但是他没有.我是说,
but he didn't.I mean he really wanted to start over with this girl with
他真想跟那女孩从头开始.因为他确实喜欢她.
a clean slate.Because he really likes her.
杰森:后来呢?
Jason: What happened?
迈克:她把他赶出去了.
Mike: She kicked him out.
杰森:可怜的埃迪.
Jason: Poor Eddie.
迈克:我是说他做了什么了?
Mike: I mean what else could he have done?
我以为有个好结果的.
I mean it should have worked out ok.
杰森:你去告诉他,迈克,
Jason: Well you got to tell him Mike, you know,
你知道,在成人世界里的事情有时是不确定的.
sometimes there are things in the adult world that cannot be fixed.
但是不要让埃迪有一分钟的怀疑,他做对了事情.
But don't let Eddie doubt for one minute that he did the right thing.
迈克:好的.晚安.
Mike: Yeah.Goodnight.
杰森:哦,迈克.还有事情你可以替我告诉埃迪.
Jason: Oh Mike.Something else you can tell Eddie for me.
迈克:好的.
杰森:他是我儿子,我很骄傲.
00:22:36,400
Mike: Yeah. Jason: I'm very proud he's my son.